https://www.winterfieldsafes.co.uk/terms-and-conditions/

Terms & Conditions
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
COVID-19 Update: We are currently unable to offer our Delivery & Position and Delivery and Installation services. Any new orders placed with either service will be contacted to advise further and may be cancelled. All products with our standard Kerbside delivery service are still available. However, there maybe some delay and longer lead-times.
During this time our highly trained sales and customer service team will be able to help you either by emailing help@sixty.co.uk or calling 0345 034 6483.
links
About Us
Customer Service
Blog
My Account
Log In
Contact Us
Winterfield Safes
Search:
All Categories
Safes
- Home Safes
- Fireproof Safes
- Budget Safes
- Hotel Safes
- Deposit Safes
- Insurance Approved Safes
0345 034 6483Mon-Fri / 9:00AM - 5:00PM
0item(s)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
0345 034 6483Mon-Fri / 9:00AM - 5:00PM
Home
Safes
Home SafesFireproof SafesBudget SafesHotel SafesDeposit SafesInsurance Approved SafesHigh Security SafesEurograde SafesLuxury SafesWall SafesUnder Floor SafesVehicle Safes
Best Buy							Chubbsafes DuoGuard Grade 1 350E
Only
Excl. VAT:
£2,149.17
Incl. VAT:
£2,579.00
Excl. VAT
Incl. VAT
(Show Excl. VAT)
Storage Cabinets
Key CabinetsFire Resistant Filing CabinetsFireproof CupboardsData Storage
Fire Rating
30 Minutes
60 Minutes
90 Minutes
120+ Minutes
Lock Type
Electronic Keypad
Key
Best Buy							Phoenix Fire Ranger FS1511 K
Only
Excl. VAT:
£524.17
Incl. VAT:
£629.00
Excl. VAT
Incl. VAT
(Show Excl. VAT)
Gun Cabinets
Shotgun CabinetsRifle CabinetsAmmo & Pistol Safes
Gun Capacity
1-2 Guns
3-5 Guns
6-8 Guns
9+ Guns
Lock Type
Electronic Keypad
Dual Key
Key
Best Value							JFC 3 Gun Shotgun Cabinet
Only
Excl. VAT:
£124.17
Incl. VAT:
£149.00
Excl. VAT
Incl. VAT
(Show Excl. VAT)
Portable Gun Storage
Gun SlipsGun CasesCartridge Bags, Belts & Loaders
Post Boxes
Stainless Steel Post BoxesTop Loading Post BoxesFront Loading Post BoxesPainted Post Boxes
Colour
Stainless Steel
Black
White
Green
Slot Type
Top Loading
Front Loading
Best Buy							Burton Convex Stainless Steel Post Box
Only
Excl. VAT:
£50.00
Incl. VAT:
£60.00
Excl. VAT
Incl. VAT
(Show Excl. VAT)
Brands
Buffalo River Burton SafesBurton Home SafesBurton Key CabinetsBurton Fireproof SafesBurton Hotel SafesBurton Eurograde SafesBurton Deposit SafesBurton Fire Resistant Filing CabinetsBurton Fireproof CupboardsBurton Vehicle SafesChubbsafesChubbsafes Home SafesChubbsafes Fireproof SafesChubbsafes Deposit SafesChubbsafes Fire Resistant Filing CabinetsChubbsafes Fireproof CupboardsChubbsafes Data SafesChurchill SafesChurchill Under Floor SafesChurchill Wall SafesJFCPhoenix SafesPhoenix Home SafesPhoenix Post BoxesPhoenix Gun CabinetsPhoenix Fireproof SafesPhoenix Fire Resistant Filing CabinetsPhoenix Fireproof CupboardsPhoenix Deposit SafesPhoenix Luxury SafesPhoenix Key CabinetsGuardianGuardian Canterbury RangeGuardian Heritage RangeFlambeau Outdoors
Home
Safes
Home SafesFireproof SafesBudget SafesHotel SafesDeposit SafesInsurance Approved SafesHigh Security SafesEurograde SafesLuxury SafesWall SafesUnder Floor SafesVehicle Safes
Storage Cabinets
Key CabinetsFire Resistant Filing CabinetsFireproof CupboardsData Storage
Gun Cabinets
Shotgun CabinetsRifle CabinetsAmmo & Pistol Safes
Portable Gun Storage
Gun SlipsGun CasesCartridge Bags, Belts & Loaders
Post Boxes
Stainless Steel Post BoxesTop Loading Post BoxesFront Loading Post BoxesPainted Post Boxes
Brands
Buffalo River Burton SafesBurton Home SafesBurton Key CabinetsBurton Fireproof SafesBurton Hotel SafesBurton Eurograde SafesBurton Deposit SafesBurton Fire Resistant Filing CabinetsBurton Fireproof CupboardsBurton Vehicle SafesChubbsafesChubbsafes Home SafesChubbsafes Fireproof SafesChubbsafes Deposit SafesChubbsafes Fire Resistant Filing CabinetsChubbsafes Fireproof CupboardsChubbsafes Data SafesChurchill SafesChurchill Under Floor SafesChurchill Wall SafesJFCPhoenix SafesPhoenix Home SafesPhoenix Post BoxesPhoenix Gun CabinetsPhoenix Fireproof SafesPhoenix Fire Resistant Filing CabinetsPhoenix Fireproof CupboardsPhoenix Deposit SafesPhoenix Luxury SafesPhoenix Key CabinetsGuardianGuardian Canterbury RangeGuardian Heritage RangeFlambeau Outdoors
Home
Terms & Conditions
Business Customer? Show Excl. VAT
Show Metric Units
FREE DELIVERY*Free UK delivery on all orders
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE14 day returns
GREAT CUSTOMER SERVICETalk to us for expert advice
TRUSTED REVIEWSView our customer feedback
Product was successfully added to your shopping cart.
Go to cart page
Continue
Terms & Conditions
Sixty Stores Ltd,
Langley Barn,
390 Birmingham Road,
Stratford upon Avon,
CV37 0RE
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS OF USE AND DISCLAIMER CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEB SITE (THIS "SITE").
1. Acceptance of Terms
1.1. By using Winterfield Safes website, you agree to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms, you may not use this site. Winterfield Safes reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update these terms of use, product prices and product information and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations, or updates on subsequent visits. Your placement of an order indicates your acceptance of these terms and conditions.
2. Stock availability
2.1. All stock is subject to availability.
2.2. Stock not supplied will not be charged for and we will refund you any part of the goods already paid for.
2.3. If we are out of stock we will make every attempt to contact you within forty eight (48) hours providing we have correct contact details on your order.
3. Manufacturer's Warranty
3.1. Manufacturer's warranties vary on each product.
3.2. Manufacturer information is subject to change without notice.
3.3. If the product you purchase is faulty, we may offer a repair, exchange or refund as appropriate in accordance with your legal rights.
4. Order Acceptance
4.1. All orders sent to Winterfield Safes are only accepted when you receive confirmation of receipt of your order, but only on the condition that Winterfield Safes may subsequently not be able to ship the items requested, or may decide on reasonable grounds not to do so.
4.2. Winterfield Safes reserves the right, at any time prior to acceptance, to refuse any order or any part of an order, or to require further or better information to enable it to evaluate and/or process the order. Without prejudice to the statutory rights afforded to consumers under English law, Winterfield Safes accepts no liability for any failure to ship products where this results from its inability to do so or its decision on reasonable grounds not to do so, provided that it takes all reasonable steps to notify you within forty eight (48) hours of order placement that products will not be shipped as ordered. In such cases Winterfield Safes will not process any payment or will immediately refund any payment made in full.
4.3. All orders placed may require additional verification before the order is accepted.
4.4. All product prices are displayed both inclusive and exclusive of VAT at 20%.
5. Payment
5.1. For payment by credit/debit card, we only accept recognised credit/debit cards as indicated on our web site FAQs.
5.2. Credit terms may be applied for and may be granted at the discretion of Winterfield Safes.
5.3. For credit applications we may make a search with a credit reference agency, which may keep a record of that search and may share that information with other businesses. We may also make enquiries about the Principal Directors with a Credit Reference Agency.
5.4. If credit is granted, credit terms will be strictly net on receipt of invoice.
5.5. If Credit terms are not granted by Winterfield Safes, all orders placed will be on a payment-with-order basis.
5.6. If the Customer fails to pay invoices within the period of Credit set, Winterfield Safes reserves the right to hold shipment of any further orders until payment has been received.
5.7. If the Customer fails to pay any sum when due or fails to perform under this or any other agreement with Winterfield Safes, after 7 days Notice, Winterfield Safes shall be entitled to interest on the amount due at Barclays Bank's base rate plus 5%, per calendar month.
5.8. Interest will be calculated from the due date, and Winterfield Safes is entitled to recover all extra expenses incurred including legal fees and cost of collection.
5.9. Extended credit terms may be available on receipt of written application.
6. Delivery
6.1. Winterfield Safes shall deliver your order via our chosen carrier. All prices quoted on our Web site include our Free Standard Delivery Service.
6.2. The Free Standard Delivery Service is available Monday to Friday during office hours, delivering to your building entrance on lightweight items and to a ground floor location or an upper floor location with access via a lift on heavy items. A delivery charge may be incurred on certain orders where the delivery route includes stairs.
6.3. Special delivery services may be available as a delivery option and may be subject to a charge as indicated on our Web site.
6.4. Expected delivery dates may be given for an order and are given as a guide only. Winterfield Safes cannot be held liable for any loss of business, income, losses, cost, damages, charges or expenses that may result from later delivery.
6.5. Free delivery is only available to UK mainland addresses. Additional services are available to Extremities, UK Offshore and International addresses at an additional cost.
6.6. A signature will be required to accept delivery and this signature will be used as proof that the delivery was accepted in its delivered condition. Any damage caused in transit must be reported within 24 hours of delivery to our customer services team in writing. Failure to report damage in transit after this period will result in any claim being void.
6.7. In the event delivery of your order is aborted by our carrier we will be forced to impose an aborted delivery charge. This fee is approximately 15% of the total cost of your order and will be confirmed in writing should the need arise.
An aborted delivery can be due either to missing delivery information such as more steps at the delivery address than originally stated on your order or out of service lifts, inaccessible doors. If you feel there may be any problems with your delivery please inform us as soon as possible to avoid any unnecessary charges.
7. Installation
7.1. Items sold by Winterfield Safes may require installation according to the manufacturer's instructions in order to meet the manufacturer's specifications or recommended cash rating. Prices quoted exclude installation unless otherwise stated. It is the buyer's responsibility to ensure the product is installed appropriately.
7.2. In all cases it is the buyer's responsibility to ensure that floor loading restrictions are adhered to. Winterfield Safes will not be held responsible for any loss or damage as a result of floor loading limits being exceeded as a result of the installation of any of its products.
7.3. Winterfield Safes offers an installation service whereby we arrange work to be performed by an appropriately qualified installer. Winterfield Safes will not be held responsible for any loss, damage or expenses incurred during, or as a result of, the product installation.
7.4. If you choose to use our installation service the delivery route and installation location must be free of obstructions, allowing easy access for our engineer. If a wall installation is required you must remove skirting boards and any other obstructions prior to installation. Failure to adhere to these instructions may result in an aborted installation.
7.5. In the event of an aborted installation the installation charge will NOT be refunded.
8. Returns Policy
8.1. Purchases may be returned to the company for a refund within 14 calendar days.
8.2. All returns must be reported via our website’s online return form.
8.3. Goods shall be returned to Winterfield Safes or their named agent. ANY POSTAGE AND PACKING COSTS INCURRED ON RETURNED ITEMS ARE FOR THE BUYERS ACCOUNT AND ARE NON-REFUNDABLE.
8.4. In order to receive a refund, your purchase must be returned in "as-new" condition, with original packaging and with all manuals and accessories.
8.5. You will receive a refund excluding the original delivery charge and any collection or re-stocking fees applied by the supplier.
8.6. Please allow up to twenty eight (28) days for refunds to be processed and credited to your account.
8.7. Exclusions to the Returns Policy: "made to order" items which include keyed alike locks, cut keys and lockers are not covered by our Returns Policy. We are unable to provide any return period on "made to order" items.
8.8. Exclusions to the Returns Policy: "bespoke" items which include products that have been specifically modified from standard specification are not covered by our Returns Policy. We are unable to provide any return period on "bespoke" items.
9. Service, Support and Complaints
9.1. Winterfield Safes provides a Customer Support Line telephone number and Customer support email address, which deal directly with most enquiries. Contact information can be found on the contact us page of our website.
9.2. We aim to reply to all complaints within forty eight (48) hours. We will provide a likely timescale for resolving the dispute and keep you informed about progress.
10. Disclaimers and Limitations on Winterfield Safes
10.1. WITHOUT PREJUDICE TO STATUTORY RIGHTS AFFORDED TO PURCHASERS OF PRODUCTS, THE INFORMATION AND MATERIALS CONTAINED IN THIS SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TEXT, GRAPHICS, AND LINKS, ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITH NO WARRANTY, AND IN PARTICULAR, Winterfield Safes DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE INFORMATION ACCESSIBLE VIA THIS SITE IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT, OR THAT USE OF THE SITE IS FREE OF RISK OF VIRUSES OR OTHER DAMAGE.
10.2. PRICE AND AVAILABILITY INFORMATION IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE. PRODUCTS PURCHASED FROM Winterfield Safes AND RELATED SERVICES, WHICH ARE PROVIDED BY Winterfield Safes, ARE WARRANTED IN ACCORDANCE WITH LAW, AND NOTHING HEREIN IS TO BE TAKEN TO EXCLUDE OR RESTRICT ANY RIGHTS, WHICH RIGHTS, WHICH APPLICABLE LAW GRANTS TO CONSUMERS IN RESPECT OF SUCH PRODUCTS OR SERVICES. INDIVIDUAL PRODUCTS MAY BE THE SUBJECT OF ADDITIONAL WARRANTIES OR GUARANTEES GIVEN DIRECTLY BY THEIR MANUFACTURERS. SUCH WARRANTIES ETC. ARE NOT ENFORCEABLE AGAINST Winterfield Safes, BUT ONLY AGAINST THE COMPANY/PERSON GIVING THEM
11. External Sites
11.1. This site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third party vendors and other third parties (the "external sites"). Winterfield Safes is not responsible for the availability of, or the content located on or through, any external site, nor for any transactions between you and such sites (including as to 'cookies', personal data, confidential information, or purchases of goods or services). You should contact the site administrator or Webmaster for those external sites if you have any concerns regarding such links, content or transactions.
12. Copyright
12.1. This site is owned and operated by Sixty Stores Ltd, unless otherwise specified all rights in the site design, text, graphics and other content, interfaces, and the selection and arrangements thereof belong to Sixty Stores Ltd or its licensors.
12.2. All rights are reserved save as set out below. Permission is granted to electronically copy and to print hard copy portions of this site for the sole purpose of placing an order with Winterfield Safes or using this site as a shopping resource. Any other use of materials on this site, including reproduction for purposes other than those noted above, modification, distribution, or republication, without prior written permission of Winterfield Safes is strictly prohibited.
13. Jurisdictions and Venue
13.1. You agree that, any dispute between our parties will be, governed by the laws of England , without regard to its conflict of law principles.
13.2. You agree that the sole jurisdiction and venue for any litigation arising from your use of or orders made on Winterfield Safes web-site shall be an appropriate court located in England.
14. Privacy Policy
14.1. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).
14.2. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.winterfieldsafes.co.uk because this Web site wants to disclose its information practices and demonstrate its commitment to your privacy.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement please contact us.
14.3. If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information such as name, email, billing and shipping addresses and financial information such as credit card number and expiration date if paying by credit or debit card.
We use this information for billing purposes and to fulfil your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
At the time of ordering you may also subscribe to our email newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe and the option not to receive our newsletter. Please see the point 15.4 below regarding opting-out of promotional communications.
14.4. We will not email you in the future unless you have given us your consent and we will provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. Additionally we offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our contact us page or you may contact us by phone to opt-out.
14.5. We use outside shipping companies to fulfil orders, and a credit card processing company (HSBC Global Payments - Sagepay) to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. Due to the size and weight of the products we supply certain items may be dispatched directly from the manufacturer warehouse. In these instances we will provide the manufacturer with your shipping and contact details to allow delivery. Manufacturers do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
14.6. We do not share, sell, rent, or trade your personally identifiable information with third parties for any unknown or unrelated uses.
14.7. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
14.8. We use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This includes using a "cookie" which is a small text file stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use two types of cookies, session ID cookies and persistent cookies.Session ID cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate our site and store items in your shopping basket. A session ID cookie will expire when you close your web browser and leave our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time and enables us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.If an order is placed we link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while placing your order. As an example, if you performed a search on Google and visited our website and made a purchase the persistent cookie would tell us that Google was the website where you found us. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file or by using the Microsoft Help & Support page: How to delete cookies. If you disable cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited. You may also experience difficulties adding items to your basket and if this is the case you should order via phone.
14.9. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Winterfield Safes, only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.
14.10. To ensure your security we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. By using Secure Socket Layer technology or SSL as it is more commonly known all data entered on our online order form such as address or credit card number is encrypted and transferred securely. Furthermore our payment security is provided by Geotrust providing additional security. However no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
14.11. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
14.12. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or if your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by contacting us or by contacting us.
15. Your Statutory Rights
15.1. Your Statutory Rights are not affected. This statement does not confer upon you any additional legal obligations or duties, it merely highlights existing rights that consumers have whenever they deal with traders.
16. Coupon Codes
16.1. We reserve the right to suspend/discontinue coupon codes without prior notice.
16.2. Promotional material, such as site wide banners, do not guarantee a product is eligible for the stated promotion.
16.3. Coupon codes will only be applied to qualifying products during checkout.
16.4. We reserve the right to decline any order made using a coupon code.
Sign up to our newsletter today to receive exclusive offers and savings.
Enter your e-mail Address
Submit
By subscribing you agree to the terms in our Privacy Policy.
© 2020 Winterfield Safes | Sitemap
WAIT! We have a special offer just for you...
We don't want to see you leave empty handed, therefore we have arranged the following special offer just for you.
Get an extra 5% OFF your entire order with coupon code SAVE5.
All Burton products are excluded from this offer. Terms & conditions apply.
Continue Shopping
